1000bulbs.com 2019-07-18

# Privacy Policy | 1000Bulbs.com

1000Bulbs.com is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect your personal information.

### 1000BULBS.COM’s Commitment to Security

1000BULBS.COM encrypts billing information wherever requested online. Personal information is accessible only by staff designated to handle complaints or requests. All 1000BULBS.COM agents and contractors with access to personal information are also bound to adhere to this policy as part of their contract with 1000BULBS.COM.

### Personal Information that 1000BULBS.COM May Collect

1000BULBS.COM collects the following types of personal information: names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone and facsimile numbers, billing information, and complaint and inquiry information. 1000BULBS.COM may also collect business information from sole proprietorships some of which might constitute personal information, as well as personal information from individuals acting solely in their business capacity. 

1000BULBS.COM does not collect or maintain information from those actually known to be under the age of 13, and no part of our site is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.

### How 1000BULBS.COM May Use Personal Information

Unless you consent, 1000BULBS.COM will use your personal information for the purpose for which it was submitted such as to reply to inquiries, handle your complaints and process billing and business requests, and we will use such information to provide operational notices, and in program record-keeping and to conduct research on industry marketplace practices. Our research will not result in the reporting or publication of any personal information provided to us. 

### How Your Information May Be Shared

Consumer inquiries may be forwarded by email, and consumers should recognize that this method of transmission may not be secure. 1000BULBS.COM may also use your personal information to research industry marketplace practices. Just as in any research we may do, 1000BULBS.COM research will not result in the reporting or publication of any personal information. 

### 1000BULBS.COM never sells or rents personal information.

We will also release personal information under the following circumstances:

  * Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation, or is requested by an agency for governmental investigative purposes or governmental proceedings
  * Where our records indicate a company may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of
  * To appropriate persons, where your communication suggests possible harm to others.

### Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate

If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information we may have on file, please email us with the new information or your review request. Let us also know the department or 1000BULBS.COM program that led to your submission of personal information so we may efficiently locate your information.

### Computer Tracking and Cookies

Our web site is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by its visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our site. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. Cookies are also used to single out users and send personalized advertising based on their browsing experience. To learn more or opt out of shared cookie pool emails, visit [www.criteo.com/privacy](https://www.criteo.com/privacy).

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. 1000BULBS.COM uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forms. Our cookies do not generate personal data, do not read personal data from your machine and are never tied to anything that could be used to identify you.

### Problems

If you have a complaint about 1000BULBS.COM’s compliance with this privacy policy, please contact us.
